Hello hello everyone, today we will give you
live serial term plans of Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance.
Aditya Birla Sun Life
is a joint venture company of Aditya Birla Capital
and
this company is a very good insurance
company and does its business in many entries.
Talking about the settlement rates, let's
start the review of the company's cars at 04.
Talking about the entry, there is
option
135 and also
Sure and option
2468 25 years maximum Varva
Single. In limited,
you can make premium payment before 60 years even regularly. You can also
select regular premium payment for the number of years for which you decide your policy.
Talking about the minimum policy term and maximum policy term, they are
according to the options which we are putting on the screen,
you can check it, it is different,
you can take a screenshot of it.
Talking about the premium mode, it can be done in monthly, quarterly,
half yearly and yearly in all the payment modes.  You
can avail the minimum
sum assured in the famous display is 25 lakhs and there is no limit on the maximum sum assured, whatever
your eligibility is, according to your income and
age, according to the guidelines of the underwriting rules,
you can get the maximum
term and the policyholder has a lot of flexibility in this plan, there is a provision for the term assured, he
can select this plan according to his needs, so let's
talk about the first option in which
your level term insurance, which means
whatever you decide in MS Word and for
whatever period you decide, there will be
no time increment in it
and in case of death, the
nominee of the policy holder will get the entire term and the selected amount in full, the
second
option in this plan is level term
insurance, whatever is the premium,
it will be the same but in this
you can add additional
premium, if the policy holder has any
concern
due to this, then all the premiums will be waived and the
policy will not be waived and if the policy  If the
holder dies, then the
nominee will get the sum assured as decided by Ruby Sameshwar. The
third option in this plan is
Increasing Term Insurance.
According to this, you can increase your insurance amount by
5 to 10 percent every year,
whichever you find comfortable. You can increase
your insurance amount without increasing the
premium. For example, if you have taken a term insurance of Rs 1 crore,
if you
select an increasing term insurance of 5 percent and
next year your insurance amount will be Rs
10,500,000, then according to this, whatever
percentage you decide, it will keep increasing. The
next option
in this plan is Increasing Term Insurance with the
premium of which the benefits of this option will
remain the same, but in case the policy
holder is diagnosed with a critical illness
or suffers a permanent disability
due to an accident, then all the future
premiums will be waived and the policy will
continue till 65. The next option in this plan is
Decreasing Sum Assured. If you feel
that your liability will be fulfilled by a certain time,
then you will get Term Insurance.  If you do
not have the requirement of premium then you
can select this option in which
your insurance amount will be decreased after one inch,
which we are entering on the screen, it is
different according to the age, you can check it. The
next option of this plan is
Decreasing Time Short Withdrawal Premium, which is the
fifth benefit, will
remain unchanged and in this, in case of critical
illness or permanent disability
due to accident, then all the future
premiums will be waived. The next option
in this plan is Return of Premium. If the
policy holder feels that the
amount paid to him on maturity should be
different, then he
can select this option. In this you have to keep in mind that
whatever premium is different to you,
it is returned to you after excluding the expenses of discounts, riders and underwriting. The
next option is
Splendor, Return on Premium Waiver
Premium, which is an option along with benefit
in every situation, all the premiums will be waived.
If you want your
partner to subscribe to this plan  If you want to add your partner in the policy,
which can be a
considerable percentage, this should be on the person you
want and
you
can select this option only in 1234. If you have
taken Airtel policy before, then the company tells
you that you can increase the sum assured
by 50% at the time of marriage,
whose maximum limit
is 50 lakhs. In the situation of having the first child,
25 percent and the maximum limit is 25
lakhs. And in the situation of having the third child,
25 percent and the maximum limit is 25 lakhs.
Talking about death benefit, if the policy
holder dies, then
in which form can the nominee get the amount? The
first option is lump sum, which is whatever
you have decided at the time, the
family will get it at the same time after the
contract is over. The second option is
lump sum plus annual income. If the policy holder
dies, then the full amount will be paid in MS Word at the
same time and the remaining amount will be paid in MS Word.  The
remaining amount will continue to be paid on an annual basis for the next 10 or 15
years, whatever you decide. The
third option is
lump sum plus increasing. If the policyholder dies, then the remaining amount will be paid at the same
time.
Your remaining amount will continue to be paid in the next 90 years, whatever you
have decided, and the
remaining amount will continue to increase every year at 5% simple interest. The
next feature of this plan is terminal
illness, which is inbuilt in this plan. If the
policyholder is diagnosed with any such disease,
after which the policyholder can
survive for a maximum of 6 months, and the doctor
certifies it, then it is
called terminal illness. In that situation, the
policyholder will get 50% of the additional amount at the same time,
and all future
premiums will be withdrawn.
In the event of the policyholder's death, the
remaining amount will be paid to the nominee,
which is inbuilt in this plan.  The feature is that
you can also add riders in this plan, by paying an
extra premium you
can increase your protection.
You can take Accidental Death and Disability Benefit Riders,
Medical Entrance Riders,
Hospital Crop,
Surgical Care Riders,
Accidental Death Benefit Transfer Additional
Addition. You have to keep in mind that there are
depreciating and
decreasing options which cannot be included in them.
If for some reason you are
not able to pay the premium and your policy lapses,
then you can revise your policy within five years by doing
them and fulfilling them on behalf of the company. If we
talk about suicide, then if the policy
holder commits suicide, then it is made
that whatever has been decided in MS Word will be returned completely. There is
no guarantee
because if you have selected the option of
return premium, whatever
return you get will be presented to the policy holder after excluding GST,
riders and underwriting expenses of the premium.
Whatever you pay on the premium is covered
under section 80C.  You
can claim tax benefit if you feel that
you have not selected the right plan, then after the free
look period which is 1538, you
can cancel your plan and get your money refunded, so
like this bike review of Aditya Birla Sun Life's lifetime plan,
if you liked the video,
we keep bringing such information, so
please like our channel and
subscribe, thank you for